module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What is the surface area of the moon?', 
    a: '4 billion acres',
    b: '2 billion acres',
    c: '8 billion acres',
    d: '9 billion acres',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many moons could fit inside the earth?', 
    a: '69',
    b: '54',
    c: '49',
    d: '33',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'When a month has 2 full moons the 2nd is called:', 
    a: 'Harvest Moon',
    b: 'Full Moon',
    c: 'Blue Moon',
    d: 'Moon Pie',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What mineral fills the dark spots on the moon?', 
    a: 'Basalt',
    b: 'Olivine',
    c: 'Pyroxene',
    d: 'Cigarette Ash',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How much did the astronauts\' suits weight on the moon?', 
    a: '30 lbs',
    b: '80 lbs',
    c: '150 lbs',
    d: '180 lbs',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How much did the astronauts\' suits weight on earth?', 
    a: '30 lbs',
    b: '80 lbs',
    c: '150 lbs',
    d: '180 lbs',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year did the last man on the moon set foot there?', 
    a: '1983',
    b: '1972',
    c: '1969',
    d: '1997',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Buzz Aldrin\'s first name?', 
    a: 'Edward',
    b: 'Edwin',
    c: 'Eduardo',
    d: 'James',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'How far is the moon from earth?', 
    a: '238900 mi',
    b: '310600 mi',
    c: '330500 mi',
    d: '401860 mi',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How much bigger is earth than the moon?', 
    a: '10 times',
    b: '7 times',
    c: '6 times',
    d: '4 times',
    answer: 'd'
  }
];